[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "I think it's a great comeback.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Nike", "Piers"]}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "Is that an advised position for Nike, do you think, to say that look, in the end, winning is all that counts, it supersedes everything, even the kind of marital disharmony that he went through?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "That is so typical of Nike, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Nike"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "Do you think that a more relaxed, happy Tiger has been the answer to a lot of his problems?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "VBN", ",", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Yes, you know, that's possible.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tiger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Paterno"]}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CD", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 122, "question": "What is the purpose of the film that you are making?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Well, first of all, there is already a film made called \"The Framing of Joe Paterno Part One.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Do you think Jerry Sandusky is a pedophile?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry Sandusky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ":", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "So why would you want to give him the oxygen of being able to talk about his victim?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Well, actually -- wait a minute.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "You don't remember slapping towels yourself, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "I'm not actually sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "You're sure you never saw Mike McQueary?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "I am sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike McQueary"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "How does that have anything to do with Joe Paterno?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Here's how.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Paterno"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Did you not say that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "I'll tell you what, let's take a break.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Did you not say that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "See if you can calm down.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry Sandusky"]}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "You don't dispute that Jerry Sandusky abused boys in the shower and this boy in particular in the shower, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Jerry Sandusky as I said in the previous segment had his day in court.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry Sandusky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Do you know why Joe Paterno was fired?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "He was allegedly fired for not protecting the very boy whose interview I'm holding in my hand, the day he got fired that there was nothing -- no reason to protect him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Paterno"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sandusky"]}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "You are going to quote the Penn State Board of Trustees?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "An employee claimed Sandusky abused a young boy in the shower.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Penn State Board of Trustees"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "How do you know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "Because he reported it to the board.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "How much money you making from it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Zero.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 279, "question": "You don't make any money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "This is --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Did you make any money from NBC?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "No, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NBC"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "You didn't make a single penny?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "Not a single penny.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "WP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Your motivation seems to be to clear Joe Paterno, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "I'm trying to figure out what the truth of the matter is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Paterno"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Please stop being such an idiot, OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "I want to find out the truth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "On behalf of the man you say you are trying to clear his name, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "I'm trying to find the truth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "You are now attacking his family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "Why are you so keen to make these victims go through more pain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "That's exactly my motivation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "If he had done any more to stop Sandusky over years of abusing boys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "RBR", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "He didn't know that was happening.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sandusky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry Sandusky"]}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "What do you think did occur then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "I believe that Jerry Sandusky and the victim say almost exactly the same thing occurred.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2012"], "ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"], "PERSON": ["Sara Ganim"]}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Can you explain why he testified the way he did or allowed Mike McQueary to testify?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Let me bring in somebody else who knows all about this, CNN correspondent Sara Ganim who won a 2012 Pulitzer Prize for our coverage this story.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike McQueary"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "What is your take on what my guest has been saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "You know, piers, here's the deal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "What does it say about this country that two young boys could even consider perpetrating such a crime?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "You know, it's a shame that our children grow up around children like this, and that children can actually grow up and do things like this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Do you have any doubt that the two that have been charged are the ones that committed this crime?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "I have no doubts that the shooter they have in custody -- I've seen his photo on another reporter's cell phone of the man that they have in custody.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ",", "VBG", "IN", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "How would you like to remember his short life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "Alive, walking around, waking me up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "When you hear that two young American boys have been charged with murder, one of whom is alleged to have gone up and shot that woman's baby in the head in a stroller, what is going wrong that can allow that mentality?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CD", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "I think it's a loss of values.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "And the way that this is moving in America so fast now in favor of gay rights and gay people getting the same rights as everybody else, would you have gone through the same kind of abyss?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "I think the attitude towards gay rights has changed so dramatically.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Do you look at him and think redemption, I've been there, know what it's like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "EX", ",", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "I try, Piers, at this point in my life not to be in serious judgment of any person except myself, and to try to do good as I see it ought to be done.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Do they deserve redemption?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "They also deserve punishment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130325pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "RBS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "Tavis, let me ask you, fascinating clip there from you show, but what do you do about these two kids in Georgia who have murdered a bay in a stroller?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "I've been watching most of your show tonight, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Georgia"]}}]